We have come to Tottori Prefecture!
We are here!
I'm here, but...
Oh, wow!
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
It's amazing.
It's fun!
I'm Madoka Saito from Tea Horse
I'm Tsuiroko.
I'm here in Tottori Prefecture.
I'm here. How do you like it, Rocco?
Well, Tottori is famous for the Tottori Sand Dunes.
I'm very happy to be here because it's a place I've always wanted to visit!
And Madopi wanted to come here so badly.
I've always wanted to come to Tottori, and I've been saying I wanted to go to Tottori.
Not only the Tottori Sand Dunes, but also me.
When I came to Tottori Prefecture, I found that the Tottori Sand Dunes in Tottori Prefecture are very famous.
It's a sacred place for my favorite anime.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
I'd like to go there.
I've been looking forward to visiting there today.
I want to enjoy Tottori.
But that's not all.
Of course, I'd like to look for some tea cakes, too.
So I'm going to go there now.
So I'd like to start from Tottori city.
It's only 9:00 a.m. right now, right?
That's right, it's very early in the morning.
I woke up very early, didn't I?
So I'd like to go have breakfast now.
I'm hungry.
But I ate around 4:00 a.m.
Yeah, I ate at 4:00, too.
That's why I'm really hungry.
The world could turn into Tottori. I want something Tottori-esque.
I'm just hanging around, but it's warm.
It's close to Tottori Station right in front of where we are now.
Tottori Station is right in front of where we are today... and what are you doing here?
Tottori Conan Tottori Sand Dunes Tottori Conan Sand Dunes This is the airport Tottori Sand Dunes Conan Airport Tottori Sand Dunes
Tottori Sand Dunes
So our first stop is Jean Sunaba Coffee!
Let's go! They have morning coffee too!
Looks delicious!
I think I'll have orange juice!
I usually drink orange juice.
I want a sweet one.
I don't drink bitter.
I want to drink orange juice and matcha ore wiener!
I'll have a set drink with orange juice at French Morning.
And a caramel waffle.
and a matcha ore wiener with ice cream.
I recommend the matcha ore wiener ice cream.
Yes, sir.
Well then...
It's actually that one.
I was going to wear a T-shirt with my guess's face on it.
But my parents told me not to because it would blind Rocco.
That's totally fine.
I'll wear a T-shirt too.
You should have worn it.
I'll wear one too.
But that stuffed animal...
I brought my stuffed animal.
For the photo.
It's been a long time coming.
I'm so happy.
But I want to ride the Lac Ladan.
Oh, it's you.
Hey! Here you go!
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh!
Cute!
So cute!
Oh, my God, it's so cute!
Cute. I'll take a picture.
It's important.
I'm famous for not taking pictures with liars.
That's why we don't have any pictures.
I know, but you have to be willing to take a picture.
I know, but if you don't think about it.
You forget.
It's huge.
It's too big.
It's too big for my face.
Too big.
Looks cute
It's too cute
too big
It's from Momochan, too.
It's from Matcha, so it's from tea
Because it's tea
Bon appétit!
Looks really delicious!
Looks so delicious!
So cute!
I ordered the caramel waffle and
and matcha orebina ice cream!
I ordered the morning set
French sauce and
set with orange juice.
Delicious!
It's good!
No, this is huge.
It's huge!
I'm really hungry here.
Bon appétit!
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
Oh, waffles are really good. They're delicious. I haven't had waffles in ages. Bon appétit.
Is it on my mouth?
It's called "done.
I think it's possible.
It's warm, plus...
The waffle batter is really sticky.
And the caramel topping
the caramel topping and the cream go so well together.
melt-in-your-mouth feeling.
Delicious!
So cute!
It's so cute that it's on your mouth.
I always get something on my mouth.
I fixed it.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
I get nervous at times like this.
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Delicious?
It's soaked into the bread.
It's delicious.
It's good.
It's good. It's so good.
It's amazing.
Delicious.
Yummy.
Yummy. Yummy.
There's one more.
That's all we got.
Oh, no.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
all done!
Finished!
Yay!
It was so good!
I'm going to go now.
Dunes?
These are dunes, too, by the way.
I got a part.
I found it.
Now!
So we're at the Tottori Sand Dunes. First time at the Tottori Sand Dunes.
First time.
It's so bright!
It's so bright, it's almost blinding.
I can't open them!
I don't know. The weather's too nice.
It won't open. You have to take precautions against sunburn.
I'm wearing sunscreen.
It's 25 degrees.
Is that so?
It seems so.
My eyes just opened like this.
Around here, maybe.
It starts here.
It says, "Beware of sun stroke." Oh, no!
I'm so tired.
It's too early.
We're going up a lot of stairs.
We've got a lot of stairs.
Wow!
Wow.
Oh, my God.
It's 36 degrees?
Wow, that's amazing.
Thirty-six degrees?
Wait, 36 degrees? No way!
It was 36 degrees, not 35.
I don't know if I can handle 36 degrees.
Oh, my God.
Wait! The ocean is so beautiful!
It's so beautiful!
It's a little dry.
So smooth!
So beautiful!
Oh, my God!
Oh, it's beautiful!
Is it this beautiful?
It's so beautiful!
Wanna go?
I did!
I didn't realize how big Japan is.
Take your bag with you one time.
Take it.
Walk with it.
Oh, no!
It's cooler than I thought.
Wait, I don't know if I'm gonna be okay.
I'm a little scared.
It's a little bit in there.
Oh, my God.
I'm really scared.
Are you sure you want to go?
Oh, my God.
Look at it like this.
It's like a sandy beach. It's kind of emo.
It's totally desert.
Litter!
It's a desert!
Oh, no! It's real!
It's a bucket!
Wait, what?
It's an "S.
That's it... that's it.
That's right, that's what I'm talking about.
I'm still not there yet.
It's still not enough.
That's why it's so high.
Feet.
There are footholds...
Mountains...
Even if there are still some hills...
The footholds are solid.
But here...
It's pretty bad.
It's all trues and sand.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
The ocean is really beautiful.
The ocean is...
It's so big.
I can see that.
It's all connected, right?
Yeah, it's amazing.
I've been living in a very small place.
No, I don't think so.
There's no sea in Saitama.
No sea.
That's right, no sea.
When you come to a place like this, you feel
The greatness of the sea.
I understand.
Yes, I do.
The air is nice.
We're going up now.
Yeah, now.
From here.
It might be the real thing now. This is where it starts.
Yeah, now, you know, it's flat.
That's pretty amazing.
Hey.
And, you know, from about 100 meters away.
Oh, long term
Oh no!
And there's no handrails or anything, right?
Yeah, yeah.
This is where the real work begins.
Up here.
Oh, wow.
No, it's from here.
That's pretty tough, huh?
It's getting a little steep.
Oh, no.
It's getting harder and harder.
The sand is really dry.
It's like Mt. Fuji, but dumber.
Fuji?
No, there isn't.
No. 5.
I've seen it from behind.
You've seen it from a car?
Oh, man.
It's kind of lame from the back, I guess.
Some of them look like rocks.
It's not a rock? It's a lump.
There's a lump.
But I think I get why they said to watch out for heat stroke when you go in there.
I think I get it.
It could take you with it.
Oh, my God, look at the back.
It's so cute.
That's amazing. - Wow.
We're just getting started.
It was a little cooler downstairs.
It's getting hotter.
That's great.
Thanks for the footprints.
Thank God.
It's like, "Okay, I'm just going to walk along here.
Wait a minute, even with the camera like this, it's pretty wide back there.
Yeah, it's great.
Beautiful.
Oh, man.
Wow.
Stingray 2.
Oh, my God.
I'll do it. Put, uh-uh.
I'm going twice as fast as I used to.
I'll be right here...
Wow!
Dazzling!
The wall is getting stronger.
It's dazzling. Wow, it's great. Feels good.
Great. I have bangs, too.
We, we, we, we... We create our own.
Happiness. There's no shame in being a dweeb.
We're us, we're us, we'll always be Eva, we'll always be Eva.
Myriads of japasillas shining in my heart.
Good luck with that chest-thumping.
Hey.
Bring a bunch of bosses.
Timing's all over the place.
Innocent personalities
All clashing with each other.
But it's still fun
Every day is new
Exciting and exciting
An unexpected marriage
There must be someone waiting for us somewhere in the world
Hey...
Let's get goosebumps and japanese pimples
With this singing voice
us
Thank you for watching!